Squirming in their seat, glancing around the room and never looking you in the eye.
在座位上扭来扭去，环顾房间，从不直视你的眼睛。
We think we know when someone is lying to us, but do we really?
我们以为自己知道别人何时在撒谎，但我们真的知道吗？
A study published in the Personality and Social Psychology Review showed that people's ability to tell if someone is lying to them is little better than 50%.
一项发表在《人格与社会心理学评论》上的研究显示，人们判断某人是否在对自己撒谎的能力仅略高于50%。
Interestingly, other research suggests that we are actually quite good at unconsciously spotting liars, but our conscious thoughts overrule this. Forensic Scientist R.
有趣的是，其他研究表明，我们实际上相当擅长无意识地发现说谎者，但我们的意识思维会推翻这一点。
Edward Geiselman points out that training in recognising liars doesn't always help, saying "quick, inadequate training sessions lead people to over-analyse and to do worse than if they go with their gut reactions".
法医学家R·爱德华·盖塞尔曼指出，识别说谎者的训练并不总是有帮助，他说："快速、不充分的培训课程会导致人们过度分析，结果比凭直觉反应更糟。"
One reason for this may be 'truth bias'.
其中一个原因可能是"真相偏见"。
Experts have suggested that we are usually biased to believe that people are telling us the truth, at least in most contexts.
专家指出，我们通常倾向于相信人们对我们说的是真话，至少在大多数情况下是如此。
Another reason that might make us bad at identifying liars is that there are a number of myths around body language and lying.
另一个可能使我们不善于识别说谎者的原因是，关于肢体语言和说谎存在许多误解。
Many of us believe that liars are unlikely to look us in the eye or will fidget in their seat.
我们许多人认为说谎者不太可能直视我们的眼睛，或者会在座位上坐立不安。
However, this isn't necessarily the case.
然而，情况并非总是如此。
Professor of psychology Kevin Colwell suggests that liars often work hard to disguise these behaviours.
心理学教授凯文·科尔韦尔指出，说谎者常常努力掩饰这些行为。
It may be that not looking away, or sitting more still than usual, are actually the giveaways that someone is not telling the truth.
实际上，不转移视线，或者比平时坐得更安静，才可能是某人没有说实话的迹象。
To see how someone's behaviour really changes as they lie, many experts recommend observing people talking about things known to be true.
为了观察某人撒谎时行为如何真正变化，许多专家建议观察人们谈论已知真实的事情。
This allows us to establish a baseline of their normal behaviours while speaking.
这使我们能够建立起他们说话时正常行为的基线。
Any differences to this baseline behaviour could show that someone is lying.
任何偏离这一基线行为的变化都可能表明有人在撒谎。
This is why it's much harder to lie to people who know us well.
这就是为什么向熟悉我们的人撒谎要困难得多。
As liars may be working hard to conceal their behaviours, some psychologists have suggested increasing the effort needed for this by asking them to tell their story backwards.
由于说谎者可能正努力掩饰自己的行为，一些心理学家建议通过要求他们倒叙故事来增加所需付出的努力。
When faced with this increased cognitive load, any behavioural tell-tale signs are magnified.
当面临这种增加的认知负荷时，任何行为上的破绽迹象都会被放大。
It can be hard to spot liars.
识别说谎者可能很难。
We are likely to trust people, and behaviours can be hidden, but if we know someone well, and if someone is working too hard to stick to their story, it's possible to see through people who are not telling the truth.
我们倾向于信任他人，而行为也可能被隐藏，但如果我们很了解一个人，并且某个人过于努力地坚持自己的说辞，那么看穿那些没有说实话的人是有可能的。